businesswolf.org 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy – Business Wolf

**Overview**

This privacy policy applies to Kshitij E-Learning ([www.businesswolf.org](http://businesswolf.org/)) on all platforms (web, mobile web, apps, emails).

Business Wolf contains links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects Personally Identifiable Information (PII).

Business Wolf takes privacy concerns seriously. This privacy policy outlines what information is collected when you visit our site.

Business Wolf gathers information about its users mainly to enhance their experience on the site and on email newsletters. This information is used to bring you content that is relevant to your interests. Additionally, Business Wolf, along with our advertising partners, gather information about you anonymously to provide you with more targeted advertising messages that are catered to your location and interests. You can opt out of information gathering for advertising purposes below.

 **Information Collected**

 ** _Personal Information/ Information You Directly Provide To Business Wolf  (BW):_**

When registering, commenting, or signing up for newsletters, you may provide Business Wolf with personal information, including but not limited to:

  * Personal contact information (name, zip code, e-mail address, phone numbers)
  * Comments
  * User names (including social media user names)
  * Correspondence with Business Wolf staff
  * Billing Information (for paid Business Wolf products)

You are not required to provide Business Wolf with any personal information in order to use the site. All information that is collected is the sole property of the site, and that information is not distributed outside of the site unless required by law.

 ** _Non-Personal Information Automatically Collected_**

This type of information is collected anonymously through the use of tracking technology using third-party cookies, web beacons, and other similar methods. No Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is collected through this methodology. This information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Hardware/software information (geographic location, IP address, browser type, device type, operating system, bandwidth, etc.)
  * Analytics information (time spent on site, number of pages viewed, referring web page, browsing information, etc.)
  * Advertising information (type of ads seen, number of times ads were served, pages where the ads were served)
  * Information collected through HTML cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies.

 ** _Information Collected Through Third-Party Sources_**

This type of information is collected anonymously by approved third-party partners (such as online marketing firms, research companies, social media companies, ad targeting firms, and other partners). None of the information collected by these sources contains any PII. This type of information includes but is not limited to:

  * Demographic information (gender, age, HHI, job title, interests, etc.)
  * Advertising information (clicks, interactions, post-impression performance data)
  * Social networking information (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc.)
  * Research information (data collected from partners such as Nielsen, Comscore, Quantcast, etc.)

 **What Is Done With The Collected Information?**

 _Email Communications_ : Business Wolf may use the information that you submit to send you email communications, such as newsletters, breaking news, information about the site, alerts, and promotional messages from advertising partners.

 _Site Analysis:_  Business Wolf uses the information collected through third-party sources to learn and analyze how the site is used. We use this information to enhance the site by making improvements based on the data collected.

 _Advertising_ : Display Ads are delivered from our adserver, DoubleClick, powered by WPP’s Real Media Group. At times third-party information is used to deliver targeted ads to you, your location, and your interests. We also use Third-Party Ad Platforms (such as Google AdSense) to deliver ads on our site. No PII is exchanged with any type of advertising message on Business Wolf

 **How We Share Information Collected**

There are very few specific circumstances when your information is shared outside of the company, these circumstances include but are not limited to:

  * If you comment or use the Facebook app on Business Wolf, the information you submit (including your social media user name, etc) is viewable to the public.
  * Business Wolf may need to disclose personal information to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or any other legal process.
  * We employ third-party services to distribute email newsletters and these third-parties have access to specific information only for the purposes of fulfilling contracts on our behalf
  * In the event Business Wolf goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

 **Email Policy**

Business Wolf does not allow any third-party company to use your email address for commercial purposes without your expressed permission. We will send you newsletter communications, partner sponsorship messages, account alerts, and any other emails you have requested to receive. If you would like to opt-out of any specific newsletters or mailings, please check your mail to change your newsletter settings.

 **Notices**

 _Children Under 13_ : Business Wolf does not knowingly target adverting to, or collect information from children under the age of 13.

 _Data Retention_ : Your personal information is retained for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy.

 _Security_ : Business Wolf uses all reasonable means to safeguard data against unauthorized use and theft.

 _Changes to This Policy_ : Business Wolf may at any time change this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes in our practices, service offerings, or market regulations. If the policy is updated, we will update the Effective Date at the top of the policy.

 _Questions/Suggestions_ : If you have any questions or suggestions for this Privacy Policy, please contact the editor of Business Wolf or email questions to [prashantranjan.sahay@gmail.com](mailto:prashantranjan.sahay@gmail.com)  
**Cookies**

A cookie (otherwise known as an HTTP cookie) is a small piece of code which can be sent from a web site or banner ad and stored on a user’s web browser. The cookie stores data such as preferences, previous activity, and other information. For more information on HTTP cookies and other online advertising definitions please visit the [IAB’s web site](http://www.iab.net/insights_research/1494).

 **For More Information**

Below are links to the privacy policies of some of our partners and links to advertising opt outs.

 **Contact Us**

If you have questions about privacy or any grievance relating to the processing of information provided by you, you may please contact us at grievance@businesswolf.org or write to us at

 ** _Grievance Redressal Officer_**  

Kshitij E-Learning

Level 5, Srei Tower,

Anath Road, Electronic City,

Near bharti Airtel Building,

Gurgaon, Haryana
